bandwidthplace.com 2014-06-25

# Bandwidth Place | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

At BandwidthPlace.com, your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website, www.BandwidthPlace.com. On some pages, you can order products, sign up for website, news, submit a feedback form, and services, make requests, or participate in surveys. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:

  * Name
  * Business name
  * Addresses
  * E-mail address
  * Phone numbers
  * Credit/debit card information (online orders only)
  * The nature of your inquiry or comment
  * Business profile information for Business Quote Request
  * Other types of feedback and information when needed to provide a product or service you requested.
  * IP address

## How BandwidthPlace.com Uses Information

We use the information you submit or otherwise provide about yourself on our website for the purpose of sending or responding to information you requested. By submitting or otherwise providing information on our Website, you are authorizing BandwidthPlace.com to collect, save, transmit, transfer, use, deliver and otherwise process such information for marketing, administration, statistical analysis, research, promotions and other purposes deemed necessary or appropriate by BandwidthPlace.com, including, without limitation, transmitting or otherwise transferring such information outside the country or geographic region in which you reside. By submitting or otherwise providing information on our website, you are authorizing BandwidthPlace.com to send you information and other communications via email and telephone related to your request, inquiry, or order.

Except as noted in this Privacy Statement, we do not share the information you submit or otherwise provide about yourself on our website with third parties unless it is necessary to complete your request or order, it is necessary to provide a product or service to you, or we want to provide you with updates and other information that we think may be of interest to you. We will also share such information with third parties if it is necessary to protect our rights or property or if it is required by law.

We use return e-mail addresses to respond to e-mail inquiries and to confirm orders or quote requests. Except as noted in this Privacy Statement, such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with third parties. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Finally, we use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and provide aggregate statistics relating to speed test results and to share with advertisers. For example, we may report that a number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that a certain number of people filled out a certain type of request, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals, except as noted in this Privacy Statement. Or, we may provide non-identifying aggregate statistics and performance results of the number of people that used the speed test tool, connecting with a certain broadband provider or technology in a certain region of the world.

### Opt-Out Policy

BandwidthPlace sends out news, product, promotional and response-type information based on the interests you have specified through:

  * Feedback Form
  * Connect with Us Form
  * Request for Business Quote
  * Request for Residential Services Quote
  * Contacted us via email

You can Opt-out of communications with BandwidthPlace.com in two ways:

  * Fill Feedback form located on every page of the site. Enter the email address you used when requested information, giving feedback, or requesting other services. Select “general” as the topic, and enter “remove” in the comments section.
  * You may select the opt-out link provided in email communications.

### Links

Our Web site may contain links to other Websites. Please be aware that this Privacy Statement does not apply to such linked sites nor is BandwidthPlace.com responsible for the content or privacy practices of such linked sites.

### “Cookies”

Like most websites, BandwidthPlace.com uses “cookies” for several legitimate purposes. These include remembering IDs and passwords, tracking user traffic patterns, and differentiating between repeat and new users. It is BandwidthPlace.com’s policy that data generated by cookies will be used for internal purposes only and to improve our website and site-related services. (A cookie is a small data file containing certain information and is written on your hard drive when you visit a website. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie).

### Third Party Cookies

BandwidthPlace.com uses advertising to create a free speed test and broadband news site. Our advertisers use cookies for a number or purposes including to avoid showing you the same ads repeatedly, to detect and stop click fraud, and to show ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as ads based on websites you have visited). Learn more about advertiser cookies, how to control your advertising-related preferences, you can access information [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ "Google Adenses Privacy Policy").

### Amendments

BandwidthPlace.com may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Any such amendments will be posted on our website.

### Inquiries

If you have any inquiries regarding this Privacy Statement, contact us.
